(Episode 14)
(الحلقة 14)
Hong Ju, don't worry. I've got it all figured out.
هونغ جو، لا تقلقي. لقد فهمت كل شيء.
I'm here to see the Chairman right now,
أنا هنا لمقابلة رئيس مجلس الإدارة الآن.
so I want you to come a little later. Got it?
لذا أريدك أن تأتي لاحقاً قليلاً. هل فهمت؟
Please accept my formal bow, Chairman.
أرجو أن تتقبلوا انحناءتي الرسمية، سيدي الرئيس.
A formal bow?
انحناءة رسمية؟
I've come to bid you a final farewell.
لقد جئت لأودعكم الوداع الأخير.
What's all this? "Final" farewell? Goodness!
ما هذا كله؟ وداع "نهائي"؟ يا إلهي!
Mrs. Yeom, are you leaving?
سيدتي يوم، هل ستغادرين؟
Oh my, are you sick? You don't look well.
يا إلهي، هل أنت مريض؟ لا تبدو على ما يرام.
Are you in a lot of pain?
هل تعاني من ألم شديد؟
Here, have a seat. Go on, sit down.
تفضل، اجلس. هيا، اجلس.
What's the point of living in this cruel world?
ما جدوى العيش في هذا العالم القاسي؟
I was nearly 40 when I first met you,
كنتُ في الأربعين من عمري تقريباً عندما التقيت بك لأول مرة،
but before that, because of my husband's gambling habit,
لكن قبل ذلك، بسبب عادة زوجي في المقامرة،
I had to run away with Hong Ju and barely managed to get a divorce.
اضطررت للهرب مع هونغ جو، وبالكاد تمكنت من الحصول على الطلاق.
Then I met CEO Chae and started working as her coordinator...
ثم التقيت بالرئيسة التنفيذية تشاي وبدأت العمل كمنسق لها...
I already know all of that.
أعرف كل ذلك بالفعل.
And I had to put up with all of CEO Chae's abuse.
وكان عليّ أن أتحمل كل إساءات الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
There were times I felt so hopeless that I would swallow my pride...
كانت هناك أوقات شعرت فيها باليأس لدرجة أنني كنت أبتلع كبريائي...
and just wanted to die.
وكان كل ما يريده هو الموت.
But the only reason I could grit my teeth and keep going was...
لكن السبب الوحيد الذي جعلني أستطيع أن أتحمل وأستمر هو...
for my one and only daughter, Hong Ju.
إلى ابنتي الوحيدة، هونغ جو.
I've lived to see her succeed.
لقد عشت لأرى نجاحها.
I know that.
وأنا أعلم ذلك.
And being by your side like this,
وأن أكون بجانبك هكذا،
serving you, has been an honor.
لقد كان شرفاً لي أن أخدمكم.
I gave CEO Chae a piece of my mind. Is she still keeping you away from here?
لقد وبّختُ الرئيسة التنفيذية تشاي بشدة. هل ما زالت تمنعك من الدخول إلى هنا؟
- Is that what this is about? - Now I'll never be...
- هل هذا هو المقصود؟ - الآن لن أكون أبداً...
able to see you again.
أتطلع لرؤيتك مجدداً.
Now I'm being sent far away to India to waste away from sickness.
والآن يتم إرسالي إلى الهند لأصاب بالمرض وأتلاشى.
What are you talking about? India?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟ عن الهند؟
CEO Chae...
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي...
has transferred my Hong Ju to India.
لقد نقلت سيارتي هونغ جو إلى الهند.
I have no idea what she's supposed to do in that faraway land.
ليس لدي أدنى فكرة عما يفترض أن تفعله في تلك الأرض البعيدة.
My daughter and I will go to India and just die, Chairman.
سأذهب أنا وابنتي إلى الهند ونموت هناك يا رئيس.
She transferred Hong Ju to India?
هل نقلت هونغ جو إلى الهند؟
And she did it without even consulting me?
وفعلت ذلك دون حتى استشارتي؟
I'm sure CEO Chae thought long and hard about it.
أنا متأكد من أن الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي فكر في الأمر ملياً وبجدية.
But at the end of the day,
لكن في نهاية المطاف،
this is about her determination to tear you and me apart.
الأمر يتعلق بعزمها على تمزيقك أنا وأنت.
What else could this be...
ماذا يمكن أن يكون هذا غير ذلك؟
but the result of her ambitious and "thoughtful" scheming?
لكن ما هي نتيجة تخطيطها الطموح و"المدروس"؟
I wonder what Lawyer Kang looks like.
أتساءل كيف يبدو المحامي كانغ.
He's here.
إنه هنا.
- Come on in. - Oh my gosh, what do I do?
- تفضل بالدخول. - يا إلهي، ماذا أفعل؟
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you all. My name is Kang Baek Ho...
مرحباً. يسعدني لقاؤكم جميعاً. اسمي كانغ بايك هو...
Welcome.
مرحباً.
What?
ماذا؟
You!
أنت!
- It can't be. - Rude Pervert?
- لا يُعقل. - منحرف وقح؟
- The Rude Guitar? - What's going on?
- الغيتار الوقح؟ - ما الذي يحدث؟
Do you two know each other?
هل تعرفان بعضكما البعض؟
Jang Mi, what's going on?
جانغ مي، ما الذي يحدث؟
Hey, why did you call him a jerk?
مهلاً، لماذا وصفته بالوقح؟
What is all this?
ما هذا كله؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
- It's nothing? - It's just we have a history.
- لا شيء؟ - الأمر فقط أن بيننا تاريخاً.
We just know each other from around,
نحن نعرف بعضنا البعض من خلال الجوار فقط.
but I didn't expect to see you here.
لكنني لم أتوقع رؤيتك هنا.
Tell me about it.
أخبرني عن ذلك.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
You've run into Lawyer Kang before?
هل سبق لك أن التقيت بالمحامي كانغ؟
What a small world. Come on, have a seat. Please, sit down.
يا لها من دنيا صغيرة! تفضل، اجلس. من فضلك، اجلس.
Yes, Mr. Oh. Ms. Jung, you said you like roses, right?
نعم، سيد أوه. آنسة جونغ، قلتِ إنكِ تحبين الورود، أليس كذلك؟
I hate flowers.
أكره الزهور.
The thorns will prick you. I prefer cookies.
ستؤذيك الأشواك. أنا أفضل البسكويت.
- Let's all sit down. Yes. - Yes.
- لنجلس جميعاً. نعم. - نعم.
(Seeking witnesses)
(طلب شهود)
My apologies.
أعتذر.
I will make sure it's taken down by the end of the day.
سأحرص على إزالته بحلول نهاية اليوم.
Make sure there are no slip-ups this time.
تأكد من عدم حدوث أي أخطاء هذه المرة.
And check for any security cameras in the area.
وتحقق من وجود أي كاميرات مراقبة في المنطقة.
- Yes, don't worry. - They just won't quit.
- نعم، لا تقلق. - إنهم لن يتوقفوا.
That was so long ago.
كان ذلك منذ زمن بعيد.
All this time has passed, and they're still at it, causing a scene?
كل هذا الوقت قد مر، وما زالوا مستمرين في إثارة المشاكل؟
They're like weeds.
إنهم مثل الأعشاب الضارة.
You pull them out, you stomp on them, but they stubbornly pop right back up.
تسحبهم للخارج، وتدوس عليهم، لكنهم يعودون للظهور بعناد.
Weeds, determined to ruin my flower garden.
الأعشاب الضارة، مصممة على إتلاف حديقة أزهاري.
That's why we have to rip them out by the roots...
لهذا السبب علينا أن نقتلعهم من جذورهم...
before they can even sprout.
قبل أن تنبت حتى.
Why aren't you eating?
لماذا لا تأكل؟
I was just enjoying watching you eat.
كنت أستمتع بمشاهدتك وأنت تأكل.
Kang Baek Ho, have you been starving or something?
كانغ بايك هو، هل كنت تعاني من الجوع أم ماذا؟
We've eaten together a million times, but I've never seen you eat like this.
لقد تناولنا الطعام معاً مليون مرة، لكنني لم أرك تأكل بهذه الطريقة من قبل.
You're not putting on a show for Jang Mi, are you?
أنت لا تقدم عرضاً لجانغ مي، أليس كذلك؟
Tae Pyung, why are you dragging me into this?
تاي بيونغ، لماذا تورطني في هذا؟
No, it's just that it's all so delicious, I can't help but inhale it.
لا، الأمر فقط أن كل شيء لذيذ للغاية، لا أستطيع إلا أن ألتهمه.
- Seriously, it's all so good! All of it! - I know, right?
- بصراحة، كل شيء رائع! كله! - أعرف، صحيح؟
Jang Mi and Suk Hee are fantastic cooks.
جانغ مي وسوك هي طباختان رائعتان.
Here, have some more.
تفضل، خذ المزيد.
- Go on, eat up. All of it. - I think I'm going to explode.
- هيا، كُلْها كلها. - أعتقد أنني سأنفجر.
But I just can't stop.
لكنني لا أستطيع التوقف.
Would you like me to get you some more?
هل ترغب في أن أحضر لك المزيد؟
No, I'm good, thank you.
لا، أنا بخير، شكراً لك.
But I have to say, Jang Mi, your cooking is the best.
لكن عليّ أن أقول، يا جانغ مي، إن طبخك هو الأفضل.
My mom made the japchae.
أمي هي من صنعت الجابتشاي.
Japchae is my specialty. Jung Suk Hee makes a mean japchae.
الجابتشاي هو تخصصي. جونغ سوك هي تُعدّ جابتشاي لذيذًا للغاية.
Oh, really?
أوه حقًا؟
But it seems like such a waste for me to have all this to myself.
لكن يبدو لي أن امتلاك كل هذا لنفسي هو إهدار كبير.
Don't lay it on too thick.
لا تضع طبقة سميكة جداً.
No, I'm serious. I'd love to eat like this every day.
لا، أنا جاد. أتمنى أن أتناول الطعام بهذه الطريقة كل يوم.
Come eat with us often.
تفضلوا بتناول الطعام معنا باستمرار.
You're helping Tae Pyung with his work,
أنت تساعد تاي بيونغ في عمله،
and you gave him that expensive guitar. We already owe you so much.
وأعطيته تلك الغيتارة الثمينة. نحن مدينون لك بالكثير بالفعل.
Then, I'll come by often and buy some side dishes.
ثم سأمرّ كثيراً وأشتري بعض الأطباق الجانبية.
Okay.
تمام.
Jang Mi, that's okay with you, right?
جانغ مي، هذا لا يزعجك، أليس كذلك؟
Of course. My brother already owes you so much.
بالتأكيد. أخي مدين لك بالكثير بالفعل.
But I hurt my hand, so it might be difficult for a while.
لكنني أصبت يدي، لذا قد يكون الأمر صعباً لبعض الوقت.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I swear, if I find the guy who did this to Jang Mi's hand, he'll pay.
أقسم بالله، إذا وجدت الرجل الذي فعل هذا بيد جانغ مي، فسوف يدفع الثمن.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Who was it that hurt your hand?
من الذي آذى يدك؟
It happened while you were working part-time at the hotel,
حدث ذلك أثناء عملك بدوام جزئي في الفندق،
so was it someone who works there?
هل كان ذلك شخصاً يعمل هناك؟
I already consulted Lawyer Kang about beating the guy who hurt you to a pulp.
لقد استشرت المحامي كانغ بالفعل بشأن ضرب الرجل الذي آذاك ضرباً مبرحاً.
Quickly talk it over with Lawyer Kang and file a complaint.
تحدث بسرعة مع المحامي كانغ وقدم شكوى.
Oh, you think I should?
أوه، هل تعتقد أنني يجب أن أفعل ذلك؟
Lawyer Kang, if you're finished eating, let's have that consultation.
المحامي كانغ، إذا انتهيت من تناول الطعام، فلنقم بتلك الاستشارة.
Hey...
يا...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
- You okay? - Yes.
- هل أنت بخير؟ - نعم.
I said you didn't have to do it.
قلتُ لكَ إنك لستَ مُضطراً لفعل ذلك.
Not at all. You treated me to such a wonderful meal.
لا على الإطلاق. لقد دعوتني لتناول وجبة رائعة.
The least I can do is wash the dishes.
أقل ما يمكنني فعله هو غسل الأطباق.
I do a great job with the dishes at home, too.
أجيد غسل الأطباق في المنزل أيضاً.
Then, I'll let you take care of it, Mr. Lawyer.
إذن، سأترك لك مهمة الاهتمام بالأمر يا سيد المحامي.
As you can see, I've hurt my hand.
كما ترون، لقد أصبت يدي.
Say no more.
لا داعي للمزيد من الكلام.
- Please, go have a seat. - What?
- تفضل بالجلوس. - ماذا؟
Dad, come on.
يا أبي، هيا.
I feel so bad making our guest do this.
أشعر بالسوء الشديد لإجبار ضيفنا على فعل هذا.
- Hey. - What?
- مهلاً. - ماذا؟
- Hey, let's go.
- هيا بنا نذهب.
- Come on. - Hey, wait a minute.
- هيا. - مهلاً، انتظر لحظة.
- Get out here. Let's go. - Hold on.
- انزل إلى هنا. هيا بنا. - تمسك جيداً.
Come on.
تعال.
Hey, just let them be alone. We should just pretend we don't notice.
يا رجل، دعهم وشأنهم. يجب أن نتظاهر بأننا لا نلاحظ.
What do you mean, Dad?
ماذا تقصد يا أبي؟
He's our guest. It's his first time over.
إنه ضيفنا. هذه أول زيارة له.
Who makes their guest do the dishes?
من الذي يُجبر ضيفه على غسل الأطباق؟
You have to give a young man and woman some time alone together.
يجب أن تمنح الشاب والفتاة بعض الوقت بمفردهما.
Didn't you see the look Jang Mi gave us earlier?
ألم تروا النظرة التي ألقتها علينا جانغ مي في وقت سابق؟
- What? - I think Jang Mi...
- ماذا؟ - أعتقد أن جانغ مي...
has a thing for the lawyer.
لديها ولع بالمحامية.
That's why she was practically pushing us out of there.
ولهذا السبب كانت تدفعنا عملياً للخروج من هناك.
No way.
مستحيل.
Lawyer Kang would be perfect for her. I'm all for it.
المحامي كانغ سيكون الشخص المثالي لها. أنا أؤيد ذلك تماماً.
I'm for it, too.
أنا أؤيد ذلك أيضاً.
I only kept quiet to save you the embarrassment.
لقد التزمت الصمت فقط لأجنبك الإحراج.
So you'd better appreciate it.
لذا من الأفضل أن تقدر ذلك.
Okay, I appreciate it.
حسناً، أنا أقدر ذلك.
It's not that I'm looking for a thank you.
ليس الأمر أنني أبحث عن كلمة شكر.
So, what are you going to do about it?
إذن، ما الذي ستفعله حيال ذلك؟
- What do you mean? - Unbelievable.
- ماذا تقصد؟ - لا يُصدق.
After what you did to my hand,
بعد ما فعلته بيدي،
are you just going to play innocent and act as if you got away with it?
هل ستتظاهر بالبراءة وتتصرف وكأنك أفلتت من العقاب؟
Are you trying to weasel your way out of this?
هل تحاول التملص من هذا الموقف؟
Hey, who says I'm doing that?
مهلاً، من قال إني أفعل ذلك؟
But that's exactly how you're acting.
لكن هذا بالضبط ما تفعله.
What do you think my family will do if they find out it was you who did this?
ما رأيك فيما ستفعله عائلتي إذا اكتشفوا أنك أنت من فعل هذا؟
- Keep it down. They'll hear you. - Hey! What are you doing?
- اخفض صوتك. سيسمعونك. - مهلاً! ماذا تفعل؟
You really are a repeat offender, aren't you?
أنت حقاً شخص يكرر المخالفات، أليس كذلك؟
Who said you could do that?
من قال إنك تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
Stop being a baby and get up.
توقف عن التذمر وانهض.
Does that give you the right to be so violent?
هل يمنحك ذلك الحق في أن تكون عنيفاً إلى هذا الحد؟
I think I need to go to the hospital.
أعتقد أنني بحاجة للذهاب إلى المستشفى.
I'm not even married yet! Will you take responsibility?
أنا لست متزوجة حتى الآن! هل ستتحمل المسؤولية؟
What?
ماذا؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Did I just hear someone scream?
هل سمعت للتو صراخ أحدهم؟
What? A scream? No, you didn't hear anything.
ماذا؟ صرخة؟ لا، لم تسمع شيئاً.
Lawyer Kang, didn't hear someone scream?
المحامي كانغ، ألم تسمع أحداً يصرخ؟
No, I didn't hear a thing.
لا، لم أسمع شيئاً.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Hong Ju, that's enough. Stop crying.
هونغ جو، هذا يكفي. توقفي عن البكاء.
You know the Chairman has high blood pressure.
أنت تعلم أن رئيس مجلس الإدارة يعاني من ارتفاع ضغط الدم.
Chairman, please don't mind what Hong Ju said.
سيدي الرئيس، من فضلك لا تهتم بما قاله هونغ جو.
It was an order from CEO Chae, so it's not like we can just reverse it.
كان ذلك أمراً من الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، لذا لا يمكننا ببساطة التراجع عنه.
Don't you worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll have a word with CEO Chae.
سأتحدث مع الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
I only reacted that way because I thought you knew, Chairman.
لم أتصرف بهذه الطريقة إلا لأنني ظننت أنك تعلم يا رئيس.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You have so much on your plate already, and I've just added to your worries.
لديك الكثير من الأمور التي تشغل بالك بالفعل، وقد أضفت أنا المزيد إلى همومك.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
- Feeling a surge of energy? - Yes.
- هل تشعر بتدفق الطاقة؟ - نعم.
There's nothing better than this for restoring your energy.
لا يوجد شيء أفضل من هذا لاستعادة طاقتك.
Welcome home, ma'am.
أهلاً بعودتك إلى المنزل يا سيدتي.
- I'm home, Father. - You. Come and sit down.
- أنا في المنزل يا أبي. - أنت. تعال واجلس.
If it isn't urgent, I'll just go change and come back down.
إذا لم يكن الأمر عاجلاً، فسأذهب لأغير ملابسي ثم أعود.
Are you trying to defy me?
هل تحاول أن تتحداني؟
No, sir.
لا يا سيدي.
Seeing Assistant Manager Jin is here,
بما أن مساعد المدير جين موجود هنا،
I assume this is about the personnel transfer.
أفترض أن هذا يتعلق بنقل الموظفين.
I will come down and explain after I get changed.
سأنزل وأشرح الأمر بعد أن أبدل ملابسي.
My goodness, CEO Chae.
يا إلهي، الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
To think she'd defy the Chairman.
يا للعجب! كيف تجرؤ على تحدي رئيس مجلس الإدارة؟
She's certainly gotten bold.
لقد أصبحت جريئة بالتأكيد.
Time for a little something sweet, isn't it?
حان وقت تناول شيء حلو، أليس كذلك؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Calculating sales gives you the biggest dopamine rush, right?
أليس حساب المبيعات يمنحك أكبر قدر من إفراز الدوبامين؟
You deserve a little reward, like some ice cream.
أنت تستحق مكافأة صغيرة، مثل بعض المثلجات.
Here, have some.
تفضل، خذ بعضاً.
- I'm fine. - You're such a stick-in-the-mud.
- أنا بخير. - أنت شخص متشبث بالرأي ومتعصب للغاية.
Are you sure you'll beat my mom's challenge to double the sales?
هل أنت متأكد من أنك ستتغلب على تحدي والدتي لمضاعفة المبيعات؟
I hope you don't get fired, Chef Kang. I want you to stick around.
أتمنى ألا يتم طردك يا ​​شيف كانغ. أريدك أن تبقى معنا.
I, Ma Seo Rin, am rooting for you.
أنا، ما سيو رين، أدعمك.
You're interrupting my work, so get out.
أنت تقاطع عملي، لذا اخرج.
Do I need to make a recording of myself saying that?
هل أحتاج إلى تسجيل نفسي وأنا أقول ذلك؟
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تظن نفسك فاعلاً؟
I don't have hepatitis or any other viruses.
أنا لا أعاني من التهاب الكبد أو أي فيروسات أخرى.
I even added my special flavor enhancer. You're welcome, right?
بل وأضفتُ مُحسِّن النكهة الخاص بي. على الرحب والسعة، أليس كذلك؟
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
Pull a stunt like that again, and I won't forgive you.
إذا كررت مثل هذا الفعل مرة أخرى، فلن أسامحك.
You're just playing hard to get. I know you liked it.
أنتِ تتظاهرين بالصعوبة. أعلم أنكِ استمتعتِ بذلك.
You know, when a girl makes a move, it's classy to just play along.
كما تعلم، عندما تبادر الفتاة بمبادرة ما، فمن الرقي أن تسايرها.
- This woman, I swear... - Okay. All right.
- هذه المرأة، أقسم... - حسناً. تمام.
I'll get out of your hair,
سأتركك وشأنك،
so hurry and eat this before it melts.
لذا أسرعوا وتناولوا هذا قبل أن يذوب.
Try all you want. It's not going to work on me.
حاول ما شئت، لكن لن ينجح الأمر معي.
What's this about transferring Assistant Manager Jin...
ما قصة نقل مساعد المدير جين...
to the India branch?
إلى فرع الهند؟
I don't understand...
لا أفهم...
why you're so upset, Father.
لماذا أنت منزعجٌ للغاية يا أبانا؟
You don't understand?
ألا تفهم؟
You know very well why you're shipping off...
أنت تعرف جيداً سبب سفرك...
Assistant Manager Jin, a good employee, to India.
مساعد المدير جين، وهو موظف جيد، سيسافر إلى الهند.
And you say you don't understand?
وتقول إنك لا تفهم؟
You're doing this to defy me just because I brought up Mrs. Yeom.
أنت تفعل هذا لتتحداني لمجرد أنني ذكرت السيدة يوم.
Since when have you defied me like this?
منذ متى وأنت تتحداني هكذا؟
Father.
أب.
Assistant Manager Jin's transfer is not under my sole authority.
إن انتقال مساعد المدير جين ليس من صلاحياتي وحدي.
And Father, instead of being disappointed with me,
ويا أبي، بدلاً من أن تشعر بخيبة أمل مني،
you should be reprimanding Assistant Manager Jin,
يجب عليك توبيخ مساعد المدير جين،
who is sitting right outside.
وهو يجلس في الخارج مباشرة.
- What? - Just look at...
- ماذا؟ - انظر فقط إلى...
Assistant Manager Jin's behavior.
سلوك مساعد المدير جين.
We're a major corporation, not some mom-and-pop shop.
نحن شركة كبرى، ولسنا متجراً عائلياً صغيراً.
She's defying a decision made by the board and the CEO...
إنها تتحدى قرارًا اتخذه مجلس الإدارة والرئيس التنفيذي...
and running to the Chairman to complain.
والركض إلى الرئيس لتقديم شكوى.
Is that appropriate for an employee?
هل هذا مناسب للموظف؟
Would I want to have someone like that working directly for me?
هل أرغب في أن يعمل شخص كهذا بشكل مباشر تحت إدارتي؟
CEO Chae!
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي!
So you're determined to get rid of Assistant Manager Jin...
إذن أنت مصمم على التخلص من مساعد المدير جين...
by sending her to India?
عن طريق إرسالها إلى الهند؟
It's not about kicking her out, Father.
الأمر لا يتعلق بطردها يا أبي.
These assignments are directly tied to an employee's career path.
ترتبط هذه المهام ارتباطاً مباشراً بالمسار الوظيفي للموظف.
And it wasn't just Assistant Manager Jin who was transferred.
ولم يكن مساعد المدير جين هو الوحيد الذي تم نقله.
So?
لذا؟
Are you telling me you're going to defy me and refuse to reverse the transfer order?
هل تقول لي إنك ستتحدى أوامري وترفض إلغاء أمر التحويل؟
Reversing the transfer order...
إلغاء أمر التحويل...
could have a negative impact on the company.
قد يكون لذلك تأثير سلبي على الشركة.
If we issue a transfer and then immediately rescind it,
إذا أصدرنا أمر تحويل ثم ألغيناه فوراً،
how could our employees possibly trust the company?
كيف يمكن لموظفينا أن يثقوا بالشركة؟
- What now? - It would confuse our employees,
- ماذا الآن؟ - سيؤدي ذلك إلى إرباك موظفينا،
and it could lower their morale and loyalty to the organization.
وقد يؤدي ذلك إلى انخفاض معنوياتهم وولائهم للمنظمة.
We'd just be shooting ourselves in the foot.
سنكون بذلك نضر أنفسنا بأنفسنا.
Father, please reconsider.
يا أبي، أرجوك أعد النظر في الأمر.
CEO Chae, how could you?
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، كيف تجرؤ على هذا؟
I've given up my days off and worked around the clock,
لقد تخليت عن أيام إجازتي وعملت على مدار الساعة.
and you know how hard I've worked for this company.
وأنت تعلم كم عملت بجد من أجل هذه الشركة.
Where are your manners?
أين أدبك؟
Have you no class, listening in on a private conversation?
ألا تملك أي ذوق، وأنت تتنصت على محادثة خاصة؟
Yeom San Wol, is this how you raised your daughter?
يوم سان وول، هل هذه هي الطريقة التي ربّيتِ بها ابنتكِ؟
No, it's just...
لا، الأمر فقط...
I'm so sorry, Chairman. She was just so distraught.
أنا آسف جداً يا رئيس. لقد كانت في حالة يرثى لها.
But, CEO Chae, Hong Ju never even took a day off.
لكن الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، هونغ جو، لم يأخذ إجازة ولو ليوم واحد.
I can guarantee you, she lives and breathes for her job.
أستطيع أن أؤكد لكم أنها تعيش وتتنفس من أجل وظيفتها.
You have no idea how hard Hong Ju has worked.
ليس لديك أدنى فكرة عن مدى الجهد الذي بذله هونغ جو.
That's what we pay her for.
هذا هو ما ندفع لها مقابله.
As if she did something so extraordinary.
وكأنها فعلت شيئاً استثنائياً للغاية.
Father, I know how fond you are of Assistant Manager Jin.
يا أبي، أعلم كم أنت معجب بالمدير المساعد جين.
I feel the same way, as does the board.
أشعر بنفس الشعور، وكذلك مجلس الإدارة.
This decision was made out of our deep appreciation for her.
لقد اتُخذ هذا القرار انطلاقاً من تقديرنا العميق لها.
Two years will fly by, and it will be a great experience for her.
سيمر عامان سريعاً، وستكون تجربة رائعة بالنسبة لها.
We made this decision with her long-term career in mind,
اتخذنا هذا القرار مع وضع مسيرتها المهنية على المدى الطويل في الاعتبار.
so please try to understand.
لذا يرجى محاولة فهم الأمر.
If you'll excuse me.
إذا سمحت لي.
CEO Chae.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
CEO Chae, please, I'm begging you. Spare Hong Ju just this once.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، أرجوك، أتوسل إليك. ارحم هونغ جو هذه المرة فقط.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
- And how exactly should I spare her? - What?
- وكيف لي أن أنقذها تحديداً؟ - ماذا؟
Come on, you know exactly what I mean.
هيا، أنت تعرف بالضبط ما أعنيه.
Hong Ju isn't strong. She can't work in a place so far away.
هونغ جو ليست قوية. لا تستطيع العمل في مكان بعيد كهذا.
You know that, don't you?
أنت تعلم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
CEO Chae, please, I'm begging you.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي، أرجوك، أتوسل إليك.
San Wol. What did I tell you?
سان وول. ألم أقل لك؟
- Yes? - I told you to never come here again...
- نعم؟ - لقد قلت لك ألا تعود إلى هنا مرة أخرى...
and to stay away from the Chairman. I believe I made that clear.
والابتعاد عن الرئيس. أعتقد أنني أوضحت ذلك.
Well...
حسنًا...
- You did. - And yet?
- فعلتَ ذلك. - ومع ذلك؟
Fine.
بخير.
So, as punishment for that,
لذا، كعقاب على ذلك،
you're exiling Hong Ju to some faraway land.
أنت تنفي هونغ جو إلى أرض بعيدة.
But don't you have a heart?
ألا تملك قلباً؟
Doesn't everyone deserve a second chance?
ألا يستحق الجميع فرصة ثانية؟
You're supposed to forgive a first mistake.
من المفترض أن تغفر الخطأ الأول.
A mistake? You call that a mistake?
خطأ؟ أتسمي هذا خطأ؟
Was getting close to the Chairman a mistake?
هل كان التقرب من رئيس مجلس الإدارة خطأً؟
Want me to record that and play it for him?
هل تريدني أن أسجل ذلك وأشغله له؟
You know that's not what I meant. Why are you doing this?
أنت تعلم أن هذا ليس ما قصدته. لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Shut up. You should know better. What are you playing at?
اصمت. كان يجب أن تعرف أكثر من ذلك. ما الذي تفعله؟
Do you think this is a joke? Don't you get it the first time?
هل تعتقد أن هذا مزحة؟ ألا تفهمها من المرة الأولى؟
- Hwa Young. - I made it crystal clear...
- هوا يونغ. - لقد أوضحت الأمر تماماً...
you were to stay away from the Chairman.
كان عليك الابتعاد عن الرئيس.
But you completely ignored me,
لكنك تجاهلتني تماماً،
and while here asking for a favor, you were seducing him?
وأثناء وجودك هنا تطلبين منه معروفاً، كنتِ تغوينه؟
And you have the gall to call that a mistake?
وهل لديك الجرأة لتسمي ذلك خطأ؟
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئاً.
Wrong about what, exactly?
ما الخطأ تحديداً؟
If you just put Hong Ju back where she belongs,
لو أعدت هونغ جو إلى مكانها الصحيح،
I'll never...
لن أفعل ذلك أبداً...
go anywhere near the Chairman again.
لا تقترب من الرئيس مرة أخرى.
I mean it this time.
أنا جاد هذه المرة.
Do you think...
هل تعتقد...
I'd choose my love over my own daughter?
هل أختار حبي على ابنتي؟
"Love?"
"حب؟"
Did you just say "love" with that filthy mouth of yours?
هل قلت كلمة "حب" للتو بفمك القذر هذا؟
Say it again. I dare you.
قلها مرة أخرى. أتحداك.
You "love" the Chairman?
هل "تحب" الرئيس؟
That's right. Love.
هذا صحيح. الحب.
I love the Chairman.
أحب رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
That's enough!
هذا يكفي!
Chairman.
رئيس مجلس الإدارة.
Chairman...
الرئيس...
Yes.
نعم.
Honey, is something on your mind lately?
عزيزتي، هل هناك شيء يشغل بالك مؤخراً؟
Honey.
عسل.
Yes?
نعم؟
Did you say something?
هل قلت شيئاً؟
I asked if something was on your mind.
سألتك إن كان هناك شيء يشغل بالك.
Why are you so spaced out? What could you be thinking about?
لماذا أنت شارد الذهن هكذا؟ ما الذي تفكر فيه؟
What's going on with you lately?
ما الذي يحدث معك مؤخراً؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
It's just a seasonal thing.
إنه مجرد أمر موسمي.
The Professor was here by himself a few days ago, too.
كان البروفيسور هنا بمفرده قبل بضعة أيام أيضاً.
The house feels so empty without the kids.
يبدو المنزل فارغاً جداً بدون الأطفال.
They'll be getting married and moving out before we know it.
سيتزوجان وينتقلان من المنزل قبل أن ندرك ذلك.
What will we do then?
ماذا سنفعل حينها؟
What do you mean? We'll just go on living, the way we always have.
ماذا تقصد؟ سنستمر في العيش كما كنا نفعل دائماً.
By the way, I heard a philharmonic orchestra was coming.
بالمناسبة، سمعت أن أوركسترا فيلهارمونية ستأتي.
Honey, we should go.
يا عزيزتي، يجب أن نذهب.
Okay, I'll look into getting tickets.
حسنًا، سأبحث في إمكانية الحصول على التذاكر.
CEO Chae is here.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي موجود هنا.
I'm just going to step out for one minute.
سأخرج لدقيقة واحدة فقط.
Where are you going at this hour?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب في هذه الساعة؟
I just need some fresh air. I feel suffocated.
أحتاج فقط إلى بعض الهواء النقي. أشعر بالاختناق.
What's gotten into him?
ما الذي أصابه؟
Wait, you got a job here?
لحظة، هل حصلت على وظيفة هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
You have to start small to make it big.
عليك أن تبدأ صغيراً لتنجح كبيراً.
CEO Chae.
الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
What?
ماذا؟
Professor.
أستاذ.
You've had a lot to drink. You should stop now.
لقد شربت كثيراً. يجب أن تتوقف الآن.
Are you worried about me?
هل أنت قلق علي؟
The only person in this whole world who worries about me...
الشخص الوحيد في هذا العالم كله الذي يقلق عليّ...
is you, Professor.
أنت هو، يا أستاذ.
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء ما؟
You seem to be drinking more than usual, CEO Chae.
يبدو أنك تشرب أكثر من المعتاد، أيها الرئيس التنفيذي تشاي.
There's always something with work.
دائماً ما يكون هناك شيء ما يتعلق بالعمل.
Today, I was just so unbearably lonely...
اليوم، شعرت بوحدة لا تطاق...
that I was about to ask the next person I saw...
كنت على وشك أن أسأل الشخص التالي الذي رأيته...
to be my drinking buddy.
أن يكون رفيقي في الشرب.
Thank you for appearing like my Prince Charming.
شكراً لك على ظهورك كأميري الوسيم.
Why is it, Professor,
لماذا يا أستاذ؟
that whenever I'm at my most desperate,
أنه كلما كنت في أشد حالات اليأس،
you always show up right on time?
هل تصل دائمًا في الموعد المحدد؟
See? You really are like a prince.
أترى؟ أنت حقاً مثل الأمير.
Here to save Sleeping Beauty?
هل جئتم لإنقاذ الجميلة النائمة؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
If you kiss me on the lips,
إذا قبلتني على شفتي،
I'll finally awaken from my slumber.
سأستيقظ أخيراً من سباتي.
And after that,
وبعد ذلك،
what happens next in the story?
ماذا سيحدث بعد ذلك في القصة؟
Hello, I'm Oh Tae Pyung.
مرحباً، أنا أوه تاي بيونغ.
I've heard about you.
لقد سمعت عنك.
We have a lot of regulars here. So an outfit like that...
لدينا الكثير من الزبائن الدائمين هنا. لذا فإن زيًا كهذا...
We're honored to be here.
يشرفنا أن نكون هنا.
We just came to introduce ourselves to you today.
لقد جئنا اليوم فقط لنعرّفكم بأنفسنا .
Starting tomorrow, we'll be dressed to impress.
ابتداءً من الغد، سنرتدي ملابس أنيقة تثير الإعجاب.
Is he your manager?
هل هو مدير أعمالك؟
Pardon?
عفو؟
Yes. He's my manager.
نعم، إنه مديري.
Give me a break.
أعطني استراحة.
I heard this will be your first time on stage.
سمعت أن هذه ستكون أول مرة لك على المسرح.
You start from the bottom and work your way up.
تبدأ من القاع وتشق طريقك نحو الأعلى.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Yes, sir!
نعم سيدي!
All right.
حسنًا.
Jang Mi,
جانغ مي،
what did you think about what Lawyer Kang suggested earlier?
ما رأيك فيما اقترحه المحامي كانغ سابقاً؟
With side dishes this delicious,
مع أطباق جانبية لذيذة كهذه،
I feel like just selling them on their own is a missed opportunity.
أشعر أن بيعها بشكل منفرد هو فرصة ضائعة.
- A business opportunity? - Yes.
- فرصة عمل؟ - نعم.
We order meal deliveries at work,
نطلب وجبات الطعام إلى العمل،
but they're loaded with artificial flavors and don't taste so great.
لكنها مليئة بالنكهات الاصطناعية ولا تتمتع بمذاق رائع.
Half the time, I'm not even sure if I should be eating it.
في نصف الأوقات، لا أكون متأكدًا حتى مما إذا كان ينبغي عليّ تناوله.
If you started a boxed lunch delivery, I think it would be a massive hit.
إذا بدأتَ خدمة توصيل وجبات الغداء المعلبة، فأعتقد أنها ستحقق نجاحًا هائلاً.
Boxed lunch delivery?
خدمة توصيل وجبات الغداء المعلبة؟
Dad, I'm all for it.
أبي، أنا موافق تماماً.
He even said he'd take care of...
بل إنه قال إنه سيتولى أمر...
the permits, health department, and all the legal stuff.
التصاريح، ووزارة الصحة، وجميع الأمور القانونية.
But that'll be tough. Will you be okay?
لكن ذلك سيكون صعباً. هل ستكون بخير؟
Of course. I've got your stamina, don't I?
بالتأكيد. لديّ نفس قدرتك على التحمل، أليس كذلك؟
Right.
يمين.
Let's save up quickly so you can study abroad.
هيا بنا ندخر بسرعة حتى تتمكن من الدراسة في الخارج.
I promise I'll do whatever it takes to support you.
أعدك بأنني سأفعل كل ما يلزم لدعمك.
Let's just work a little harder, okay?
فلنعمل بجدية أكبر قليلاً، حسناً؟
It's not hard work.
الأمر ليس عملاً شاقاً.
I love doing this, Dad.
أحب فعل هذا يا أبي.
(Suk Hee's Side Dishes)
(أطباق سوك هي الجانبية)
Yes.
نعم.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Is that really true?
هل هذا صحيح حقاً؟
How did this happen? Yes, I understand. Okay.
كيف حدث هذا؟ نعم، أفهم. حسناً.
Dad?
أب؟
Gosh, look.
يا إلهي، انظر.
This...
هذا...
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
The banner's gone again?
هل اختفى الشعار مرة أخرى؟
Yes. I'm positive about this now.
نعم، أنا متأكد من هذا الآن.
I'm positive it's the work of the jerks who did that to your mother.
أنا متأكد تماماً أن هذا من فعل الأوغاد الذين فعلوا ذلك بأمك.
(The First Man)
(الرجل الأول)
Maybe the culprit is still living around Taean.
ربما لا يزال الجاني يعيش في منطقة تايان.
Should we put the banner back up?
هل نعيد تعليق اللافتة؟
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
You're resigning?
هل ستستقيل؟
You're leaving Dream Hotel...
أنت تغادر فندق دريم...
to be unemployed and live with your mom?
أن تكون عاطلاً عن العمل وتعيش مع والدتك؟
I don't know. We'll have to wait and see.
لا أعرف. علينا أن ننتظر ونرى.
A singer I back is performing here today, and he insisted that I come.
مغني أدعمه سيحيي حفلاً هنا اليوم، وقد أصر على حضوري.
When he starts singing, make sure you clap really loud for him, okay?
عندما يبدأ بالغناء، تأكدوا من التصفيق له بصوت عالٍ، حسناً؟
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
(الترجمة مقدمة من KOCOWA.)